Guide to the Autograph Files, 1669-1995
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
- D
  - Damrosch, Frank, 1897-1912; (2 letters)
  - Damrosch, Walter, 1934-1944; (7 letters, 1 envelope, 1 newspaper clipping)
  - Dana, Edward Salisbury, undated; (1 envelope)
  - Dana, James D., 1864 Oct 14; (1 letter)
  - Danes, Jiro V., 1927, undated; (2 letters, 1 article)
  - Daniels, Anne Paine, 1890 Jan 8; (1 letter, 1 envelope)
  - Daniels, Josephus, 1915 May 27; (1 letter)
  - Darr, M.M., 1914 Apr 3; (1 letter)
  - Darrah, William Culp, 1948 Nov 1; (1 letter)
  - Darwin, Sir George Howard, 1897 Nov 1; (1 letter)
  - Daves, Graham, 1896 Dec 11; (1 letter)
  - Davis, Bette, 1944; (2 envelopes, 4 letters)
    — Includes material on using women's rights pioneers as film material.
  - Davis, Rear Admiral Charles Henry, 1875 Feb 8; (1 letter)
  - Davis, Elmer, 1918-1953; (2 letters, 1 address, 1 article)
  - Davis, Gladys Rockmore, undated; (1 letter)
  - Davis, Katharine Bement, 1913, undated; (3 letters, 1 envelope)
  - Davis, Kenneth, 1944-1947; (2 letters)
  - Davis, Norman H., 1924 May 10; (1 letter)
  - Dawson, Sir William, 1875 Feb 4; (1 letter)
  - Day, Henry Noble, 1875 Feb 15; (1 letter)
  - De la Mare, Walter, 1955 Dec 28; (1 letter)
  - De La Roche, Mazo, 1936, undated; (2 letters, 1 envelope)
  - De Morgan, William, 1914 Jan; (2 letters)
  - Dean, Willard L., 1885-1891; (3 letters)
  - Deane, John H., 1885 Aug 27; (1 letter)
  - Debussy, Claude, undated; (1 letter, 1 envelope)
  - Dellenbaugh, F. S., 1922 Jan 25; (1 letter)
  - Denio, Elizabeth H., 1870 Mar 11; (1 letter)
  - Dannreuther, Gustav, [1910-1915]; (4 letters)
  - Dewell, Jessie K., 1915 Oct 28; (1 letter, 1 envelope)
  - Dewey, George, 1962; (1 letter)
  - Dewey, John, 1917-1931; (2 letters)
  - Dewey, Melville, 1888 Dec 31; (1 letter, 1 envelope)
  - Dick, Alice M., 1931; (1 letter)
  - Dickens, Charles, 1857-1861; (7 letters, 1 envelope, 1 autograph) (Box 2)
  - Dickenson, Anna E., 1863-1888
    — Includes material on her speaking engagements and personal news.
  - Dickenson, Don McDonald, 1898 Mar 28; (1 letter)
  - Dickenson, Emily, undated; (3 letters)
  - Dickinson, M.L., 1887 Sep 21; (1 letter)
  - Dimnet, Ernest, 1919-1921, undated; (4 letters)
  - Dimock, George E., 1912 Dec 17; (1 letter)
  - Ditmares, Raymond L., 1919 Mar-Apr; (3 letters)
  - Dix, Dorothy L., 1875 Feb 15; (1 letter)
  - Doane, Bishop William Croswell, 1887, 1891, undated; (4 letters)
  - Dobson, Austin, 1890 Oct 11; (1 letter)
  - Dodge, Josephine, 1911 Jun 9; (1 letter)
  - Dodge, Louise, 1904 Mar 22; (1 letter)
  - Dodge, Mary A., 1876 Sep 13; (1 letter)
  - Dodge, William Earl, 1873 Feb 3; (1 letter)
  - Dorpfeld, Fredrich Wilhelm, 1896 Oct 8; (1 letter)
  - Dorsey, Susan Miller, 1881 Jul 2; (1 letter)
  - Dos Passos, John, 1955 Oct 16, undated; (2 letters)
  - Douglass, Frederick, 1880
    — Includes material on John H. Raymond's activities on behalf of fugitive slaves in Rochester.
  - Douglas, Helen Gahagan, 1946 Feb 14; (1 letter)
  - Douglass, Norman, 1927 Aug; (2 letters)
  - Dow, Caroline B., 1929; (4 letters)
  - Dowie, Alexander, undated; (1 letter)
  - Dowling, Noel T., 1950-1951; (3 letters)
  - Drake, Durant, 1916-1924; (2 letters)
  - Draper, Ruth, undated; (1 letter, 1 playbill)
  - Dreiser, Theodore, 1931, undated; (3 letters, 2 manuscript excerpts) (Box 2)
  - Drennan, Manuel J., 1893; (2 letters)
  - Drisler, Henry, undated; (1 letter)
  - DuBois, W.E.B, 1904 May 28; (1 letter)
  - Dudley, J. H., undated; (1 letter)
  - Dumas, Alexander, undated; (1 letter)
  - DuMoulin, Frank, 1920 Mar 18; (1 letter)
  - Dutcher, Charles M., 1925-1926; (7 letters)
  - Dutcher, Mrs. Gertrude J., 1909 Jan 29; (1 letter)
  - Dwight, William B., 1885-1906; (5 letters, 1 envelope)
  - Dyer, Louise, 1955 May 7; (1 letter)
- E
  - Earle, Alice Morse, undated; (1 letter)
  - Eastman, Alvan C., 1958-1959; (2 letters, 2 envelopes, 2 pictures)
  - Eastman, Max, 1918 Oct 15; (1 letter)
  - Eastwood, Ellen C., 1900; (1 letter)
  - Eaton, Daniel Cady, 1875 Feb 18; (1 letter)
  - Eberhart, Richard, 1943-1967, undated; (3 letters, 2 poems, 1 manuscript)
  - Eddy, Sherwood, 1917 Apr 21; (1 letter)
  - Edman, Irwin, 1917; (1 letter, 1 poem)
  - Effinger, Cecil, 1959 Mar 16; (1 letter)
  - Egan, Eleanor Franklin, 1921 Nov 17; (1 letter)
  - Eggleston, George E., 1872; (1 letter)
  - Einstein, Lewis, 1924-1930; (3 letters)
  - Eisenhower, Dwight D., 1949-1957, undated; (2 letters, 1 photograph)
  - Eliot, Charles William, 1871-1920; (8 letters, 3 envelopes)
  - Eliot, Samuel A., 1915 Apr 24; (1 letter)
  - Ellis, Havelock, 1924; (1 letter)
  - Ellis, Richard, 1960 Mar; (2 letters)
  - Elmendorf, Joachim, 1885-1893; (2 letters)
  - Elson, Louis Charles, 1897 Apr 12; (1 letter)
  - Elsworth, Ethel H., 1895 Mar 24; (1 letter)
  - Ely, Richard T., 1886, undated; (1 letter, 1 signature)
  - Ely, Robert Erskine, undated; (1 letter)
  - Emerson, Ralph Waldo, 1823-1967; (2 letters; 1 signed check, framed) (Box 5 (Oversize))
  - Eulalia, H.R.H., Infanta of Spain, 1893 Dec; (1 letter)
  - Evans, Edith, 1932-1933, undated; (2 letters, 2 envelopes)
  - Evarts, Allen W., 1892-1895; (2 letters)
  - Everett, Edward, 1848-1861; (3 letters)
- F
  - Fairchild, Henry Pratt, 1944 Jun 13; (1 letter)
  - Fairchild, James H., 1870-1875; (2 letters)
  - Faithfull, Emily, 1884-1885; (3 letters)
  - Fanning, B.E., 1879 May 31; (1 letter)
  - Faraday, Michael, 1852 May 19; (1 letter, photocopy -- SEE Salmon Historical Collection for original)
  - Farrar, Frances, 1925 Sep 18; (1 letter)
  - Farson, Negley, undated; (3 letters, 2 envelopes)
  - Faunce, William Herbert Perry, 1915 Feb 20; (1 letter)
  - Faust, Frances (Patterson), undated; (1 letter)
  - Fellows, Lucia Russell, undated; (1 letter)
  - Ferrer, Terry, 1957 Dec 13; (1 letter)
  - Fessendan, Kate, undated; (1 letter)
  - Field, Henry Martyn, 1875, 1888; (2 letters)
  - Field, Kate, 1862 Sep 11; (1 letter)
  - Fields, James Ticknor, 1872 Oct 14, 1879 Mar 1; (2 letters)
  - Fillmore, Millard, 1856-1908, undated; (3 letters, 1 envelope)
  - Finch, Charlotte E., 1885 Sep; (2 letters)
  - Finch, George A., 1835 May; (2 letters)
  - Fincham, David, 1936 Jul 28; (1 letter, 1 envelope)
  - Findlater, Jane H., 1914 Dec 30; (1 letter)
  - Finley, John, 1917-1925; (6 letters, 2 envelopes)
  - Fish, Hamilton Jr., 1922-1927; (6 letters, 3 news clippings)
  - Fisher, Dorothy Canfield, 1934; (5 letters)
  - Fisher, George Park, 1888 Oct; (1 letter)
  - Fitzgerald, Francis Scott Key, circa 1936; (1 letter) (Box 3)
  - Fitzherbert, Maria Anne (Mistress of King George IV), undated; (1 letter)
  - Fletcher, Alice Cunningham, 1904 Dec 23; (1 letter)
  - Fletcher, S. Francis, 1958-1961; (1 letter, 10 poems)
  - Flexner, Simon, 1916 Apr 12; (1 letter)
  - Fliess, Peter J, 1958 Jun 23; (1 letter)
  - Flint, Austin, 1875 Feb 6; (1 letter)
  - Folger, Emily Jorden, 1895 Feb 16; (1 letter)
  - Folger, H.C., 1923 Oct 11; (1 letter)
  - Forbes, Esther, to Ruth (Fitch) Mason (VC 1912), 1944-1962; (58 letters, 31 envelopes, 2 greeting cards, 3 postcards)
  - Forbes, Marie, undated; (1 letter)
  - Forby, William F., 1879 Feb 14; (1 letter)
  - Ford, Henry II, 1956 Mar 1; (1 letter)
  - Ford, Worthington C., 1918 Apr 22; (1 letter)
  - Fortas, Abe, 1968 Jun 21; (1 letter)
  - Fosdick, Henry Emerson, 1920 Feb 3; (1 letter)
  - Foster, Roger, 1882 Jan 9; (1 letter)
  - Fox, Alanson J., 1885 May 25; (1 letter)
  - France, Anatole, 1923; (1 article)
  - Francia, undated; (1 letter, 1 photograph)
  - Frankau, Julia, 1914 Jan 1; (1 letter)
  - Frankenfurter, Felix, 1918-1939; (5 letters)
  - Franklin, Christine Todd, 1886-1937; (9 letters)
  - Fraser, Helen, 1917 Jun 4; (1 letter)
  - Frech, Jacob, 1922 Mar 12; (1 letter)
  - Fredericq, Paul, 1918 Oct 12; (1 letter)
  - Freeman, Edward Augustus, 1881-1882; (3 letters)
  - Freuchen, Peter, 1937 Mar 15; (1 letter)
  - Friedan, Betty, 1963; (2 letters)
  - Frost, Elinor, 1936, undated; (4 letters, 1 envelope)
  - Frost, John W., 1909 May 19; (1 letter)
  - Frost, Robert, 1920-1936; (3 letters)
  - Frothingham, I.H., 1870 Feb 15; (1 letter)
  - Frothingham, Octavius Brooks, 1883 Apr 19; (1 letter)
  - Fry, Elizabeth, 1836 Feb 2; (1 letter)
  - Fulbright, J.W., 1955-1959; (2 letters)
  - Furness, Horace Howard, 1890-1901; (2 letters, 1 envelope)
  - Furnivall, F.J., to Henry Noble MacCracken, 1907-1908; (23 postcards, 2 letters)
  - Fyfe, H. Hamilton, 1914 Jan 1; (1 letter)
- G
  - Gailor, Thomas F., 1919-1920; (2 letters)
  - Gale, Zona, 1921-1937; (14 letters, 2 envelopes)
  - Galsworthy, John, 1914-1925; (3 letters)
  - Gambee, Martin, 1939 Nov 7; (1 letter)
  - Gapen, Eli, 1865; (2 letters)
  - Garfield, Abram, 1949 May 2; (1 letter)
  - Garfield, James A., 1882 Mar 19; (1 letter)
  - Garibaldi, Giuseppe, 1864-1907; (3 letters, 1 envelope, 1 portrait)
  - Garner, R.L., 1892 Jun 12; (1 letter)
  - Garrison, Eleanor, 1912 Feb 10; (1 letter)
  - Garrison, Francis J., 1897 Jan 8; (1 letter, 1 excerpt)
  - Garrison, William Lloyds, 1877
    — Includes material on women's rights.
  - Gaunt, J, undated; (1 letter, 1 envelope)
  - Geer, E. Harold, 1929; (2 letters)
  - George, E.R., 1874; (1 letter)
  - Gerber, August, 1906; (2 letters)
  - Gibbon, Edward, 1784; (1 letter, 1 portrait)
  - Gideon, Miriam, 1962-1965; (7 letters)
  - Gilder, Richard Watson, 1890-1902; (3 letters)
  - Gildersleeve, Virginia C., 1943-1944; (5 letters)
  - Gilkey, Charles W, 1920 Jul 14; (1 letter)
  - Gillespie, L.P., 1910 Jun 20; (1 letter)
  - Gilman, Charlotte Perkins (Stetson), 1890-1903; (6 letters)
  - Gilman, Daniel Coit, 1880 Nov 18; (1 letter)
  - Gilman, Lawrence, 1935 Jan 25; (1 letter)
  - Gilman, Nicholas F., 1895 Apr 5; (1 letter)
  - Giraud, Jacob P., Jr., 1867-1870, undated; (21 letters, 1 manuscript)
  - Gladden, Washington, 1877-1890; (5 letters)
  - Gladstone, W.E., 1894 Mar 2; (1 letter, 1 envelope)
  - Glasgow, Ellen, 1934 Jan 14; (1 letter)
  - Godard, Benjamin, 1879 May 21; (1 letter)
  - Godchaux, Elma, 1937 Jan 5; (1 letter)
  - Goddard, Martha LeB, 1895 Sep 24; (1 letter)
  - Godey, L. A., undated; (1 letter)
  - Godkin, Edwin Lawrence, 1890 Jun 14; (1 letter)
  - Godwin, Parke, 1870-1889; (2 letters)
  - Goetschius, Percy, 1906 Oct 2; (1 letter)
  - Gogarty, Oliver St. John, 1942 Feb 10; (1 letter)
  - Goldwater, Berry, 1957 Mar 5; (1 letter)
  - Gollance, Prof., undated; (1 postcard)
  - Goodrich, Herbert F., 1950; (2 letters)
  - Goodwin, Abby M., 1889 Jun 16; (1 letter)
  - Gordon, A. McD, 1944 Jun 7; (1 letter)
  - Gosse, Edmund, 1915 Mar 20; (1 letter, 1 envelope)
  - Gottschalk, Louis Moreau, 1863 Aug 2; (1 letter)
  - Gould, John, 1875 Nov 26; (1 letter, 1 envelope)
  - Gow, George Coleman, 1897-1932; (7 letters)
  - Graham, Alice Walworth, undated; (2 letters)
  - Grand, Sarah, 1913 Jan 20; (1 letter)
  - Grant, Isabella, undated; (1 letter)
  - Grant, Ulysses S., 1890 Oct 28; (1 letter, 1 envelope)
  - Graves, Frank Pierrepont, 1917 Apr 17; (1 letter)
  - Gray, Asa, 1886; (3 envelopes, 3 letters)
  - Greely, Horace, 1867 Aug 25; (1 letter)
  - Green, Rev. Henry, 1860 Aug 23; (1 letter)
  - Green, J.A., 1862 Jun 16; (1 letter)
  - Green, M. Louise, 1896 Feb 26; (1 letter, 1 envelope)
  - Greenbie, Marjorie B., 1967-1968; (2 letters)
  - Greene, Fredrick Stuart, 1919; (2 letters)
  - Greer, David H., 1905 Feb 7; (1 letter)
  - Gregory, Casper Rene, 1898 Oct 13; (1 letter)
  - Griffis, William Elliot, 1901 Jan 28; (1 letter)
  - Griffith, R.H., 1925 Mar 29; (1 letter, 1 envelope)
  - Griggs, Edward Howard, 1936 Mar 17; (1 letter)
  - Griggs, Emily M. (VC Faculty - Music), 1866 Feb-1867 Oct; (10 letters, 10 transcripts)
    — Includes material on life and people at Vassar College.
  - Griswold, Erwin N., 1965 Mar 17; (1 letter)
  - Guthrie, Claire Riley, 1915 Oct 26; (1 letter, 1 envelope)
  - Guthrie, Ramon, 1971 Jan 8, undated; (7 letters, 1 signed poem)
  - Guyot, Arnold, 1875 Feb 5; (1 letter)
  - Gwenlock, Ruth (Bribach), 1939, undated; (6 fragments, 2 letters)
- H
  - Hackett, Francis Goodrich, 1962 May 14; (1 letter)
  - Hadley, Arthur Twining, 1879 Mar 16; (1 letter)
  - Hadley, Helen (Morris), 1897-1913; (3 letters)
  - Hadow, Sir William Henry, undated; (1 letter, 1 envelope)
  - Haggard, H. Rider, 1913 Dec 31; (1 letter)
  - Hahn, Michael, 1866 Jan 26; (1 letter)
  - Haight, Elizabeth Hazelton, 1915-1946; (14 letters)
  - Hale, Edward Everett, 1881-1907, undated; (12 letters)
  - Hale, Horatio, 1864 Feb; (1 editorial)
  - Hale, Sarah Josepha, 1851-1875; (8 editorials, 30 letters, 1 envelope)
  - Halevy, Jacques, undated; (1 letter)
  - Hall, Asaph, 1889 Feb 13; (1 letter)
  - Hall, Charles Cuthbert, undated; (1 letter)
  - Hall, Granville Stanley, 1857 Nov 26; (1 letter)
  - Hall, John, 1871-1890; (3 letters)
  - Hambleton, T. Edward, 1959 May 26; (1 letter)
  - Hamilton, Alexander, 1823 Mar 14; (1 letter)
  - Hamilton, Annie Lee, 1914 Jan 12; (1 letter)
  - Hammer, Ellen J., [1954 Apr 6?]; (1 letter)
  - Hammerich, Angul, 1897 May 3; (1 letter)
  - Hancock, John, 1775 Jun 20; (1 original document) (Box 1)
  - Hannay, James O., 1963; (1 letter)
  - Hanus, Paul H., 1895 May 26; (1 letter)
  - Harding, Mary Esther, [no year] Sep 28; (1 letter)
  - Harper, James Thorne, 1888 Jan 31; (1 letter)
  - Harraden, Beatrice, 1925 Jan 22; (1 letter, 1 envelope)
  - Harriman, Averell, 1957 Jun-Nov; (2 letters)
  - Harris, Edwin S., 1892 Mar 18; (1 letter)
  - Harris, Frank, [Missing as of February 2023]
  - Harris, Fred, 1968-1971; (2 letters, 1 document)
  - Harris, Ira, 1875 Jan 18-21; (2 letters)
  - Harris, LaDonna, 1968 Sep 4; (1 letter)
  - Harrison, F., 1907 Feb 19; (1 letter)
  - Harrison, Pamala, [no year] May 15; (1 letter)
  - Haskins, C.H., 1917 Mar 10; (1 letter, 1 envelope)
  - Hasse, Adelaide, 1908 Jul 20; (1 letter, 1 envelope, 1 document, 3 newspaper clippings)
  - Hatcher, Orie Latham, 1913-1915; (2 letters, 1 envelope, 1 document)
  - Haubiel, Charles, 1943 Apr 12; (1 letter, 1 envelope)
  - Haweis, Hugh Reginald, [no year] Oct 11-14; (5 letters)
  - Hawkins, Anthony Hope, 1914 Jan 18; (1 letter)
  - Hay, F.R., 1932 Jan 9; (1 letter)
  - Hay, John, undated; (1 letter, 1 envelope)
  - Hayes, Rutherford B., 1876-1931; (3 letters, 1 card)
  - Hays, Alice, 1885-1916; (3 letters, 1 postcard)
  - Hazard, Bertha, 1885 Jun 20; (1 letter)
  - Hazen, C.D., 1916 Dec 15; (2 letters, 1 envelope)
  - Hazen, J.C., 1885 Aug 1; (1 letter)
  - Head, Barelay V., 1898 Apr 14; (1 letter, 1 envelope)
  - Hellman, Lillian, 1979 Nov 19; (1 letter)
  - Hemingway, Mary Dimock, 1909 Feb 25; (1 letter, 1 envelope)
  - Hemotin, Ellen M., 1897 Mar 19; (1 letter, 1 envelope)
  - Henck, Alice C., 1904 Jan 14; (1 letter)
  - Henderson, Archibald, 1937 Jan 2; (1 letter)
  - Henderson, C.R., 1897 Mar 4; (1 letter)
  - Hennequin, Alfred, 1878 Oct 15; (1 letter)
  - Hericourt, Jenny, 1870 Jul 24; (1 letter, 1 copy, 1 notecard)
  - Hersey, Heloise E., undated; (1 letter)
  - Hess, Carl, 1897 May 17; (1 letter)
  - Hewitt, John, 1887 Sep 24; (1 letter)
  - Hibben, John Grier, 1912 Sep 12; (1 letter, 1 envelope)
  - Hibben, Sheila, 1986 Jul 20; (1 letter, 1 envelope)
  - Hichens, Robert, 1913 Jan 2; (1 letter)
  - Hicks, Dorothy, [no year] Mar 19; (1 letter)
  - Hicks, Granville, 1935 Feb-Oct; (3 letters)
  - Hickson, Katherine Tynan, 1914 Jan 10; (1 letter)
  - Higginson, Thomas Wentworth, 1875-1905; (11 letters, 1 postcard, 3 envelopes, 1 document)
  - Hill, E.J, 1915 Jun 23; (1 letter)
  - Hill, William Bancroft, 1900 May 30; (2 letters, 1 envelope)
  - Hinkel, Charles J., 1871-1876; (2 letters, 1 envelope)
  - Hinkle, Minnie, undated; (1 letter, 1 envelope)
  - Hisox, Helen C., 1883 May 31; (1 letter, 1 envelope)
  - Hitchcock, Roswell Dwight, 1872, 1882; (2 letters)
  - Hodge, E. Carol, 1939 May; (2 letters)
  - Hoffman, George F., 1916-1923; (4 letters, 1 envelope, 1 invitation, 2 newspaper clippings)
  - Hoffman, Paul G., 1961-1962; (2 letters)
  - Hofmeister, Fredrich, 1961-1962; (1 letter, 1 copy)
  - Holbrooke, Joseph, 1908; (1 letter)
  - Holbrook, N.H., 1887 Sep 5; (1 letter, 2 copies)
  - Holden, Ella (Webb), 1915 Oct 15; (1 letter, 1 envelope)
  - Holden, Miriam, 1947-1964; (57 letters, 5 postcards, 2 documents)
  - Holland, J.G., 1881-1895; (2 letters)
  - Hollen, Lois, 1962 Nov 1; (1 letter, 1 envelope)
  - Holler, John E., 1927 Oct 10; (1 letter)
  - Hollister, Justina (Merrick), 1909 Nov 5; (1 letter, 2 copies)
  - Holmes, Oliver Wendell, 1873-1898; (7 letters, 1 signed poem, 1 card, 1 signed photograph)
  - Holt, Hamilton, 1918 Oct 15; (1 letter)
  - Hooker, Isabella, undated; (1 letter)
  - Hooper, Franklin William, 1907 Nov 29; (1 letter)
  - Hoover, Herbert, 1920-1928; (5 letters, 1 copy, 1 envelope with speech enclosed)
  - Hopkins, Mark, 1872-1878; (2 letters, 1 envelope)
  - Hoppe, A., 1897 May 3; (1 letter)
  - Hopper, Edward, 1940 Nov 5; (1 letter)
  - Horne, Herbert P., 1892 Jul 2; (1 letter)
  - Hough, Lynn Harold, 1920 Sep 20; (1 letter)
  - Hough, Williston S., [no year] Oct 17; (1 letter, 1 envelope)
  - House, Edward M., 1922 Nov 16; (1 letter)
  - Houseman, Lawrence, 1913 Dec 28; (1 letter)
  - Hovelague, Emile, 1917 Jun; (3 letters)
  - Howard, Oliver Otis, 1903-1905; (4 letters, 1 envelope)
  - Howe, Elizabeth M. (VC 1882), 1898-1913; (10 letters, 8 copies, 3 envelopes)
  - Howe, Julia Ward, 1865-1891; (3 letters)
  - Howe, Julia Ward - Signed print of "Battle Hymn of the Republic,", 1900 Apr; (1 framed item) (Box 6)
  - Howelle, William Dean, 1869-1898; (5 letters)
  - Howland, Alice M., 1912 Jan 17; (1 letter, 1 copy)
  - Hoy, Elizabeth R., 1933 Apr 21; (1 letter)
  - Hoyt, Colgate, 1885 May 20; (1 letter)
  - Hoyt, Mary F., 1885 May 17; (1 letter)
  - Huard, Frances Wilson, undated; (2 letters)
  - Hubbard, Elbert, 1902-1926; (2 letters, 1 manuscript)
  - Hudson, William Henry, [no year] Dec 8; (1 letter, 1 envelope)
  - Hughes, Charles E., 1920-1922; (2 letters)
  - Hughes, Langston, 1934 Jan 11; (1 letter)
  - Hughes, Richard, 1925 Jul 29; (1 check)
  - Hughes, Rupert, 1931 Sep 1; (2 letters)
  - Hulburd, Alice L., 1938-1939; (3 letters)
  - Hull, Cordell, 1933-1940; (2 letters)
  - Humpstone, Mabel Hastings, 1915-1927; (2 letters, 1 envelope)
  - Huneken, James, undated; (1 document)
  - Hunt, Thomas Sterry, 1872-1875; (2 letters)
  - Huntington, A.T., 1886-1887; (2 letters, 1 note)
  - Huntington, Frederic Dan, 1871-1880; (6 letters, one handwritten copy of a letter, 1 postcard)
  - Hurst, Fannie, 1928-1959; (7 letters, 1 envelope)
  - Huxley, Julian, 1961 Mar; (2 letters, 1 pamphlet)
- I
  - Ihne, W., 1898 Jan 6; (1 letter, 1 envelope)
  - Image, Selwyn, 1893-1895; (4 letters)
  - Indy, Vincent d’, 1922 Mar 19; (1 letter, 1 translated copy)
  - Inkster, Leonard, undated; (1 letter)
  - Irving, Henry, 1893 Dec 18; (1 letter, 1 envelope)
  - Irwin, Inez Haynes, 1932 Aug 8; (1 letter)
  - Ishimoto, Shidzue, 1933 May 8-9; (2 letters)
  - Ives, Harmony, 1945 May 24; (1 letter)
  - Ives, Irving, 1948 Mar 11-15; (2 letters)
- J
  - Jackson, Helen, 1948 Jun 21; (1 letter)
  - Jackson, Robert H., 1949 Oct 5; (1 letter)
  - James, Henry, 1901-1914; (10 letters, 1 envelope)
    — Includes correpondence to Katherine Loring on having a case of the shingles, living arrangements in England, family affairs, American presidential politics, fire in Salem, Mass., European politics, literary events, Sarah Jewett, and Boston news.
  - Jamison, W.P., 1906 Jun 28; (1 letter)
  - Javits, Jacob K., 1962 Apr 13; (1 letter)
  - Jeanne-Claude (Jeanne-Claude Denat de Guillebon), 1972, 1983-1984; (3 postcards)
  - Jeffers, Robinson, 1946 Jul 16; (1 letter)
  - Jefferson, Allan A., [Missing as of February 2023]
  - Jefferson, Charles E., 1903 May 27; (1 letter)
  - Jefferson, Joseph, 1887-1902; (2 letters, 1 note, 1 envelope, 1 clipping)
  - Jefferson, Thomas, 1818-1905; (4 letters, 1 envelope, 2 copies)
  - Joachim, Joseph, undated; (1 note)
  - Johnson, Burges, 1921-1925; (4 letters)
  - Johnson, Lady Bird, 1968 Mar 15; (1 letter)
  - Johnson, Lyndon B., 1968 Mar 23; (1 telegram)
  - Johnson, Mordecai Wyatt, 1933 Mar 6; (1 letter)
  - Johnson, Samuel, 1777 Jul 7; (1 letter)
  - Jones, Howard Mumford, 1952 Jun-Jul; (2 letters)
  - Jordan, Elizabeth G., 1902 Feb 25; (1 letter, 1 envelope)
  - Jospeh, Toni (VC 1983), to Shirley Maul (VC Librarian), 1983-1986; (4 letters, 4 envelopes, 1 photograph)
  - Judson, Maragret, 1913 Jul 30; (1 letter, 1 envelope)
  - Jusserand, 1915 Jul-Oct; (3 letters, 2 envelopes)
- K
  - Kaemmel, Otto, 1898 Feb 15; (1 letter, 1 envelope)
  - Kahn, Otto, 1918-1932; (3 letters)
  - Kant, Immanuel, [Missing as of March 2012]
  - Kapp, Caccilie, 1870-1878; (6 letters, 1 postcard)
  - Karfoil, Bernard, 1940-1941; (2 letters)
  - Katzenstein, Caroline, 1963 Apr 30; (1 letter)
  - Kauffman, Dr. Phil E., undated; (1 letter)
  - Keating, Kenneth B., 1962 Mar 28; (3 letters)
  - Keats, John, undated; (1 photocopied letter)
  - Keith, Mary A., 1879 Mar 2; (1 letter)
  - Keller, Helen, 1927-1957; (4 letters, 2 envelopes)
  - Kelly, Eleanor P., 1938 Dec 21-28; (2 letters)
  - Kelly, Howard A., 1939 Feb-Apr; (1 letter, 1 newspaper clipping)
  - Kendrick, J. Ryland, 1885-1916; (8 letters, 1 envelope)
  - Kennan, 1918-1932; (3 letters)
  - Kennan, George, 1952 Nov 14; (1 letter)
  - Kennedy, John F., 1946-1961; (8 letters, 2 envelopes)
  - Kenyon, Helen, 1917 Nov 17; (1 letter)
  - Keppel, Fredrick P., 1910 Oct 17; (1 letter)
  - Kerr, Jessica M., 1973-1983; (2 letters)
  - Key, V.O., Jr., 1948 Jun 2; (1 letter)
  - Keynes, John Maynard, 1933 Jan 25; (1 letter)
  - Kin Keldey, Otto, 1946 Mar 3; (1 letter)
  - King, Charles, 1861 Feb 29; (1 letter)
  - Kingsford, Charles Lethbridge, [no year] Dec 19; (1 letter)
  - Kingsley, Charles, 1874 Mar 6; (1 letter)
  - Kirkland, Winifred M., 1905 Sep-Nov; (2 letters, 1 envelope)
  - Kittredge, G.L., 1908 Feb-Jul; (3 letters, 1 postcard)
  - Kitts, Harriet W., 1895 Nov 5; (3 copies of 1 letter)
  - Knapp, William, 1866 Nov 6; (1 letter)
  - Knight, Mariette (Barnes), 1887 Jul 16; (1 letter)
  - Knight, William, 1898 Jan 20; (1 letter)
  - Knox, Henry, 1790 Aug 30; (1 letter)
  - Koo, May T., 1916 Jul 25; (1 letter, 2 newspaper clippings)
  - Krenek, Ernst, 1943 Sep 9; (1 letter)
  - Kroeger, Ernest Richard, 1911 Sep 20; (1 letter)
- L
  - [unidentified person with the initials, C. L.], 1919 Feb 3; (1 letter, 1 envelope)
  - Ladd, Mary (Babbott), 1913 Aug 20; (1 letter, 1 envelope)
  - Lahey, Dr. Frank M., 1940 Jun 7; (1 letter)
  - Lahr, Kathleen P., undated; (5 letters)
  - Lalo, Edouard, undated; (3 letters)
  - Lamberg, Rose, 1935 May 25; (1 letter)
  - Lamont, Daniel Scott, 1888 Sep 13-14; (2 letters, 1 note)
  - Lamprecht, Karl G., 1904 Oct-Nov; (2 letters)
  - Lanciani, Rodolfo, 1886-1887; (2 letters)
  - Landauer, Bella C., undated; (1 letters)
  - Landis, James M., 1939-1943; (2 letter)
  - Landon, Alf M, 1940 Jun 24; (1 letter)
  - Landon, L.E., 1888; (4 letters, 2 clippings, 1 envelope)
  - Lane, G.M., 1899 May 3; (1 letter)
  - Lang, Benjamin Johnson, undated; (1 letter)
  - Lang, Paul Henry, 1938-1953; (6 letters)
  - Lange, Francisco Curt, 1953 Mar 17; (1 letter)
  - Langley, Samuel Pierpont, 1876 Apr 7; (1 letter)
  - Lardner, Ring W., 1924-1925; (3 letters, 3 envelopes)
  - Larrabee, Rachel, 1926 Nov-Dec; (1 letter)
  - Laski, Harold J., 1947 Mar 26; (1 letter)
  - Lasky, Bessie, 1933 Mar 1; (1 letter, 1 newspaper clipping)
  - Lathrop, Edward, [no year] May 28; (1 letter)
  - Lathrop, George Parsons, 1887 Feb 15; (1 letter)
  - Lathrop, Julia C., 1913-1923; (8 letters)
  - Lattimore, Owen, 1950 Aug-Sep; (2 letters)
  - Lavery, Emmet, 1941 Jul 23; (1 letter)
  - Lawrence, D.H., 1913 Sep-Oct; (2 letters)
  - Lawrence, D.H., 1921 Aug-Nov; (1 letter, 2 envelopes, 1 manuscript) (Box 3)
  - Lawrence, William, 1919 Mar 25; (1 letter)
  - Lea, Issac, 1862 Mar 8; (1 letter)